<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on jriver Blog and Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://jriver.xyz/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on jriver Blog and Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://jriver.xyz/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jriver.xyz/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jriver.xyz/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;bio&#34;&gt;Bio&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Jedidiah River Clemons-Johnson, though I use the moniker jriver, and river226 online. I am a Father, Software Developer/Engineer, Leader, Teacher, Snowboarder, and Techie in the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I live in the Chicago Area. I have a passion for learning new things, challenging myself, and simply exploring all things programming and tech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;projects&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;nuthttpsgithubcomriver226nut&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/river226/Nut&#34;&gt;Nut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nut or the &amp;ldquo;Nut Utility Tool&amp;rdquo; was concived of while I was working in an IT role. It intialially meant to run a script and launch a customized instance of TightVNC to match the way it was used in the company. After a while additional uses for a simple utility became apparent, and Nut became a plugin driven utility tool. Nut is designed to run in the system tray and allow access to installed plugins with a right click on the icon. This is intended to be as simple as accessing basic audio or wifi settings, and provided a consistent expirience across systems. Nut in it&amp;rsquo;s current state is in an early alpha with a lot of it&amp;rsquo;s functionality to be developed and refined. Once it is complete, there will be a proper web interface for finding and installing plugins, as well defined plugin interface&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
